Guide to the Bruce Davidson photographs, 1955-2008 RL.11753
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Bruce Davidson photographs
1955-2008
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Davidson, Bruce, 1933-
RL.11753
6 Linear Feet 4 boxes 229 photographic prints
Bruce Davidson (b. 1933) is an American-born photographer, and a member of the Magnum Photo cooperative agency. Collection consists of 229 photographic prints, mostly black-and-white, with color work present in several series. Subjects range widely, with a focus on human interactions, minority and disenfranchised communities, urban street photography, and landscapes influenced by human activity. Locations include Chicago; Paris; England, Wales, and Scotland; Sicily and Venice; Los Angeles and the California Pacific Coast Highway; and New York City, including East Harlem, Central Park, the subway, and other locations. Also included is a large series of portraits chiefly of celebrities, and images deriving from commercial assignments. Several portraits of African Americans from Mississippi, South Carolina, and New York City were taken in 1962 while Davidson was documenting civil rights actions. Other short series feature nude female studies, French fashion shows, and scenes from the film production of Zabriskie Point by Antonioni. Sizes range from approximately 6x9 to 20x24 inches. Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts at Duke University.
Arrangement
The prints are organized by bodies of work, in alphabetical order by series title. Within the series, prints are arranged in rough date order by year.
Biographical / Historical
Bruce Davidson (1933- ) is an American-born photographer and photojournalist. A member of the Magnum Photo cooperative agency since 1958, his photographs have been published and exhibited widely, and are part of major museum holdings around the world.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Bruce Davidson photographs were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2019.
Content Description
The images in this collection were taken by photographer Bruce Davidson over the course of his career, from 1955 to 2008. Genres include street photography, interiors, landscapes, and portraits, all offering a complex view into interactions between people, and between humans and natural and built environments. Most were shot in black-and-white with a large-format camera, though there are also chromogenic and dye transfer color prints in several series. Most of the series in the collection house a small selection of prints from each project; the largest series, Portraits, contains almost 50 prints.
Some of Davidson's earliest photographs were shot in Montmartre, Paris in the 1950s, where he documented the solitary life of the widow of an Impressionist painter. He later returned to Paris in 1962, 1999, and 2005. He traveled the streets of New York City in the 1960s, exploring life in the Lower East Side, East Harlem, and Central Park, and continued this work from the 1970s into the 2000s. There are several series exploring Los Angeles, dating from the 1960s to the 2000s, as well as a series of images taken in Chicago during a visit in 1989. A few images are from Venice and Sicily.
Also present is a large series featuring portraits of U.S. actors, authors, politicians, artists, a conductor, and a rock musician. This series contains the earliest work in the collection, several portraits taken in 1955 of an aging couple in Arizona. A separate series, Time of Change, contains three portraits of African American rural and urban citizens in Mississippi, South Carolina, and New York City, taken in 1962 while Davidson documented the civil rights and suffrage movements in those locations.
Other series in this collection feature images of people, animals, and landscapes in England, Scotland, and coal mining communities in Wales; portraits of passengers on the New York subways; and photographs taken at fashion shoots and at filming locations for Zabriskie Point. Also included is a series of images from commercial assignments and commissions (1983-1997).
Image titles were taken from the prints or from the Magnum Photos website; a few other titles and captions derive from donor notes. Prints with no known titles are noted as such. Significant markings on the prints are also noted, as are legacy identifiers, which include various alphanumberic codes assigned by Davidson, the Magnum cooperative, and a private collector.
The prints are unmounted and were created with traditional processes, chiefly silver gelatin (black-and-white) on paper, with large-format color work present in the Chicago and Subway series, and a few smaller color prints scattered in the Commercial and California series. Print sheet dimensions are given to the nearest 1/8 inch and include variations on 8x10, 8 1/2 x 11, 11x14, 16x20, and 20x24 sizes.
Many of the images in this collection were published in photobooks and in journalistic publications, and have been exhibited widely.
African Americans -- Mississippi -- Portraits; African Americans -- South Carolina -- Portraits; African Americans -- Suffrage; California Highway 1 (Calif.) -- Photographs; Celebrities -- United States -- Portraits; Commercial photography -- United States; Documentary Photography -- United States; Photographers -- United States; Photography of the nude; Portrait photography -- United States; Subways -- New York (State) -- New York -- Photographs; California -- Photographs; Central Park (New York, N.Y.) -- Photographs; Chicago (Ill.) -- Photographs; England -- Photographs; Los Angeles (Calif.) -- Photographs; Lower East Side (New York, N.Y.) -- Photographs; New York (N.Y.) -- Photographs; Paris (France) -- Photographs; Scotland -- Photographs; Sicily (Italy) -- Photographs; Venice (Italy) -- Photographs; Wales -- Photographs; Black-and-white prints (photographs); Chromogenic color prints; Gelatin silver prints; Dye transfer prints; Davidson, Bruce, 1933-; Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University); Magnum Photos
- California: Los Angeles, 1964; 3 prints
  Scope and Contents
  Davidson traveled to Los Angeles, California in 1964 and spent several weeks there, shooting street life, celebrities, landscapes, and architecture. He returned in 2008 to reconsider the city and its environment; these images are located in the series "The Nature of Los Angeles."
  - USA. Los Angeles, California. Gloria Swanson attending a movie premiere, 1964; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0001)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: 64-11-8/33; 48761 [119]
  - No known title, 1964; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0002)
    Other legacy identifiers: 64-11-8/3; 48760 [119]
  - No known title, 1964; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0003)
    Other legacy identifiers: 64-11-14/11; 48762 [119]
- California: The Nature of Los Angeles, 2008; 3 prints
  Three decades after his first photographic exploration of Los Angeles, California, Davidson returned to the city, again choosing to shoot black-and-white film. The series title comes from the photobook, published in 2015.
  - USA. Los Angeles, California. 405/10 Underpass, 2008; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 23 7/8 x 19 7/8 inches (60.64 x 50.48 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0004)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2008-1-84/C; 46591 [140]
  - USA. Los Angeles, California. Malibu Creek State Park, 2008; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0005)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 08-1-218/C; 48441 [113]
  - USA. Los Angeles, California. Mulholland Highway, 2008; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 23 7/8 x 19 7/8 inches (60.64 x 50.48 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0006)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2008-1-218/C; 46592 [140]
- California: Pacific Coast Highway, 1993; 2 prints
  Both of these images were shot by Bruce Davidson in color for a project documenting landscapes and people along the Pacific Coastal Highway (State Route 1) in California.
  - [Pfeiffer?] Beach at Big Sur, California, 1993; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0007)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 40/22; 46259 [134]
  - Point Reyes, California, 1993; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0008)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 72-33; 49401 [165]
- California. Zabriskie Point, 1968; 3 prints
  Davidson shot these photographs on location in California for the filming of Zabriskie Point (1970), a fictional full-length movie about youth culture directed by Michelangelo Antonioni.
  - Zabriskie Point, Marc and Daria, 1968; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0009)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 68-17; 53730 [96]
  - No known title, 1968; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0010)
    Other legacy identifiers: DAB 68-17-131/384; 46764 [136]
  - No known title, 1968; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0011)
    Other legacy identifiers: DAB 68-17-44/2199; DAB 68017C00027; 46749 [136]
- Chicago, 1989; 8 prints
  A variety of scenes shot in color on the streets and in bars make up this series on Chicago in the 1980s.
  - USA. Chicago, Illinois, 1989; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 6 3/4 x 10 inches (17.14 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0012)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: R 73-f1; 47035 [162]
  - USA. Chicago, Illinois, 1989; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 6 5/8 x 10 inches (16.82 x 25.40 cm). (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0013)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: 65f-14a; 47036 [162]
  - USA. Chicago, Illinois, 1989; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 20 x 24 inches (50.80 x 60.96 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0014)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: 46690 [142]
  - USA. Chicago, Illinois, 1989; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 20 x 24 inches (50.80 x 60.96 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0015)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: 46699 [142]
  - USA. Chicago, Illinois, 1989; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 24 x 20 inches (60.96 x 50.80 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0016)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: 46709 [142]
  - USA. Chicago, Illinois, 1989; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 24 x 19 1/4 inches (60.96 x 48.89 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0017)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: 46729 [142]
  - USA. Chicago, Illinois, 1989; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 24 x 20 inches (60.96 x 50.80 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0018)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: 46674 [142]
  - USA. Chicago, Illinois, 1989; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 20 x 24 inches (50.80 x 60.96 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0019)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: 46687 [142]
- Commercial Work, 1983-1997; 27 prints
  Images in this series represent Davidson's commissioned work for a number of enterprises, including medical research organizations, Wells Fargo Bank, and the U.S. Air Force. These images are in black-and-white, with the exception of the Wells Fargo Bank series. When present, titles originate from captions on the prints. The donor's inventory served as the source for most of the subject notes; others are from inscriptions on the prints.
  - No known title, 1983; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0020)
    Northrop. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 83-19; 51877 [147]
  - No known title, 1983; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0021)
    Northrop. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 83-19; 51879 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0022)
    Biogen. Massachusetts. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Doctor's jacket patch: "Dana-Farber Cancer Institute." Print -0022 and 0023 are duplicate images (same frame). Other legacy identifiers: DAB 86-10; 51750 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0023)
    Biogen. Massachusetts. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Doctor's jacket patch: "Dana-Farber Cancer Institute." Print -0022 and 0023 are duplicate images (same frame). Other legacy identifiers: DAB 86-10;51752 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0024)
    Biogen. Massachusetts. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Doctor's jacket patch: "Dana-Farber Cancer Institute." Other legacy identifiers: DAB 86-10;51753 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0025)
    Biogen. Massachusetts. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 86-10;51781 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0026)
    Biogen. Massachusetts. Label on print recto reads "Biogen." Subject is Dr. Thomas Charles Merigan, virologist. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 86-10;51790 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0027)
    Biogen. Massachusetts. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Dr. Thomas Charles Merigan and colleague. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 86-10;51741 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0028)
    Cray Research. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 86-2; 51799 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0029)
    Cray Research. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 86-2; 51807 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0030)
    Cray Research. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 86-2; 51810 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0031)
    Cray Research. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 86-2-20 #6; 51812 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0032)
    Cray Research. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 86-2; 51818 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0033)
    Cray Research. Source of subject note: label on print recto. Other legacy identifiers: 86-2; 51833 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0034)
    March of Dimes. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 86-21-56/3; 44706 [67]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0035)
    March of Dimes. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 86-21; 51743 [147]
  - No known title, 1986; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0036)
    March of Dimes. Source of subject note: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 86-21; 51748 [147]
  - No known title, 1990; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0037)
    ABC-TV Soaps [source of note: donor inventory]. Stamp on print verso: "Work print, not for reproduction." Other legacy identifiers: 90-2-68/10; 42401 [37]
  - 3:30-5pm Wells Fargo Bank, 1995; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0038)
    Color print. Title source: label on print verso. New York Times Story, AG Group [source of note: donor inventory]. Other legacy identifiers: 47063 [163]
  - No known title, 1995; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0039)
    Part of Wells Fargo Bank staff series. Color print. New York Times Story, AG Group [source of note: donor inventory]. Other legacy identifiers: 47071 [163]
  - No known title, 1995; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0040)
    Part of Wells Fargo Bank series. Color print. New York Times Story, AG Group [source of note: donor inventory]. Other legacy identifiers: 47089 [163]
  - No known title, 1995; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0041)
    New York Times Story, AG Group [source of note: donor inventory]. Other legacy identifiers: 47091 [163]
  - Maboud, 1995; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0042)
    Title source: label on print verso. Title may refer to the portrait's subject, who also appears in the Wells Fargo Bank series of smaller prints. Other legacy identifiers: 95-7 Maboud; 46275 [134]
  - No known title, 1983; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0043)
    Other legacy identifiers: 83-19; 48577 [116]
  - No known title, 1983; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0044)
    Other legacy identifiers: 83-19; 48579 [116]
  - No known title, 1997; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0045)
    U.S. Air Force 50th anniversary [source of note: donor inventory]. The photographer's identifiers for similar images on the Magnum Photos site indicate the location is at Nellis Air Force Base in Nevada, July 1997. Other legacy identifiers: 97-7-1/21; 44353 [66]
  - No known title, 1997; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0046)
    U.S. Air Force 50th anniversary [source of note: donor inventory]. The photographer's identifier on the Magnum Photos site for similar images indicates the location is at Nellis Air Force Base in Nevada, July 1997. Other legacy identifiers: 97-7-43/5-6; 44364 [66]
- England, Scotland and Wales, 1960-1965; 26 prints
  Many of these images, taken in 1960s, were published in Davidson's photobook, England/Scotland, published by Steidl in 2006. Included in this series is a small group of images taken in coal mining communities in Wales in 1965. Although Davidson shot some images in this series on color film, the prints in this group are black-and-white. Titles are taken chiefly from the Magnum Photos website or from the prints themselves.
  - England, Blackpool, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 9 7/8 x 8 inches (25.08 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0047)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 65-43-1/34; 53693 [96]
  - GB. England. London. Photo of Queen Elizabeth II projected on a curtain, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 7 1/2 x 9 1/2 inches (19.05 x 24.13 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0048)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Mounted on board. This is a cropped version of an image on the Magnum Photos website. Other legacy identifiers: 60-22-52/23-24; 53946 [98]
  - Scotland Oz, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0049)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 60-22-44/31A; 53633 [95]
  - London, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0050)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 60-22-51/38; 53632 [95]
  - UK. Brighton. Man on the beach alone, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0051)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 60-22-18/16; 50960 [77]
  - Scotland. Man reading paper next to window, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0052)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 60-22-175/39A; 51198 [80]. Carries Davidson's Mangum Photo stamp.
  - UK. Hastings. Old man on motorcycle, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0053)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 60-22-40/10; 50950 [77]
  - Shepherd, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0054)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 60-22-151/18A-19; 41304 [26]
  - Women's bowling on green, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0055)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 60-22-29/32Q; 601; PF105896; 50995 [77] Photo is creased vertically down the middle.
  - Scotland, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0056)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 60-22-135/16A; 41290 [26]
  - England, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0057)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 60-22-176/19; 41298 [26]. Title on Magnum Photos site is given as "Scotland."
  - UK, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0058)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 60-22-131/12A; 41299 [26]
  - No known title, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0059)
    Other legacy identifiers: 60-22-126/31; 48506 [114]
  - No known title, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0060)
    Other legacy identifiers: 60-22-101/15; 48508 [114]
  - No known title, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0061)
    From series of images from Scotland; similar image on Magnum Photos website is titled "Family of farmers." Other legacy identifiers: DAB 60-22-134/21A-22; PR000695; 48538 [114]
  - No known title, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0062)
    Other legacy identifiers: 60-22-25/6; PR000632; 48540 [114]
  - GB. England. Hastings. Couple laying on grass., 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0063)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 60-22-33/6A; 50947 [114]
  - GB. England. Hastings. Couple sitting on beach having tea, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0064)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 60-22-15/19; 50953 [77]